Support-Hotline 

If you need one-on-one attention to resolve your technical issue or question, our support team is here to help.

in Europe:
Mondays to Fridays: 9:00 a.m. to 6 p.m. CET
We can currently advise you and answer your questions in the following languages: English, French, German, Spanish and Italian. 
Tel: +49 (0)1805 12 30 12
Fax:+49 (0)1805 00 83 18
E-mail: support-eu@destinatortechnologies.com
Web Address: www.destinatortechnologies.com

in North America:
Mondays to Fridays: 9:00 a.m. to 5 p.m. EST
Tel: 1-866-798-0905 (toll free in the United States)
Fax: 1-905-764-3680
Email in Canada: supportca@destinatortechnologies.com
Email in the United States: supportus@destinatortechnologies.com
Web Address: www.destinatortechnologies.com

Pay-per-call service fees are charged to the telephone number from which the call was placed and will appear on your monthly telephone bill. This may be a per-minute charge or a flat fee. Please consult your local telephone company for details.
